各位  我有个大消息宣布
People, I have huge news!
"大"的部分是由谁带来呢
Who's carrying the rest of it in?
我找到了能促进生意的方法
I found a way to improve diner business,
更疯狂的是  居然不用炒了你俩
and the crazy part is I don't have to fire you two.
你打算要打扫女厕
Are you gonna clean that dead body smell
清掉里面的死人味了吗
out of the ladies' room?
不是  买芳香剂不就是为了这个吗
No, that's what plug-in Glade is for.
大家还记得之前的慈善冰桶挑战
Okay, remember how that ice bucket challenge
因为艺人们而爆红吗
caught on with celebrities?
阿憨  大家做那个挑战是为了帮助渐冻人症
Han, people did those challenges for ALS,
不是点评网上被称为"纯凭运气"的
not to get publicity for a diner that Yelp calls,
餐厅拿来骗人气用的
"A bit of a dice roll."
我发明了调味料挑战
Well, I've invented the condiment challenge.
为啥  是因为使用保险套[音似调味料]
Why, 'cause condoms are a challenge
对你跟其他小处男来说  难度太高吗
to you and other virgins?
厄尔  吐得一口好槽啊
Earl, you're on fire!
我要灌下番茄酱与黄芥末酱
I'm gonna down ketchup and mustard
然后再点名演员乔治·克鲁尼先生
and then nominate Mr. George Clooney.
如果你真的想这事爆红
If you really want this thing to go viral,
我刚好知道克鲁尼喜欢"是拉差辣椒酱"
I happen to know that Clooney likes him some spicy sriracha.
我只知道爆菊很火辣
All I know is that anal is hot.
人家的老婆是叫宝菊  不叫爆菊
His wife's name is Amal, not anal.
我还是支持我刚才的论点
I still stand by my statement.
开拍
Action!
又或者是所谓的"赶紧弄完了事吧"
Otherwise known as, "Let's get this over with."
乔治先生
Mr. George...
好辣
Uh-oh! I... hot!
太辣了
Too hot!
我觉得这短片还真可能会爆红呢
I actually think that could go viral.
靠  我按错按钮了
Damn! I hit the wrong thing.
阿憨  再重拍一次
Han! Han, do over!
我身体里面像烧起来啦
My insides are on fire!
我好喜欢星期三
I love Wednesdays.
因为我可以把别人
I get to erase all the genitalia
画在我们小蛋糕黑板上的鸡鸡全擦掉
that was drawn on the cupcake board.
我喜欢星期四  因为我又能重新画上鸡鸡
And I love Thursdays 'cause I get to redraw them.
我需要多一点纸巾
I need some more paper towels.
多的好像在楼下吧
Oh, I think they're downstairs.
麦克斯  你好会演假装下楼梯
Max, you do fake stairs so well.
我知道
I know.
这是我"假"得第二好的事
It's the second best thing I fake.
那不是安迪吗
Hey, isn't that Andy?
我那个安迪吗
My Andy?
天啊  还真是糖果安迪
Oh, God, it is Candy Andy.
他要过来这边了
He's coming over here.
你好啊  麦克斯
Hey, Max. Wow.
你黑板的美腿我可以玩好久啊
Your chalkboard has really nice legs.
-好啊  -我知道很傻
- Hey. - I know, so silly.
我只是不太擅长见到我的前男友们
It's just I'm not very good at seeing my exes.
你也很不擅长躲
Yeah, or hiding.
你糖果生意怎么样了
How's the candy business?
"酸"溜溜  疯颠颠[坚果]  宅男多[糖果品牌]吗
Sour? Nutty? Full of Nerds?
很不错啊  糖果们也不会跑掉
It's great. Candy's not going anywhere,
就像我奶奶膝盖上的肥肉一样
like my grandma's knee fat.
你们俩还在那间餐厅打工吗
So you guys still over at the diner?
人家才没有还在那间餐厅上工呢
We aren't still at the diner.
这里可是我们的小蛋糕橱窗
This is our cupcake window.
姐两位
Uh, hello?
你们五分钟前就该到餐厅开工了
Your shift at the diner started five minutes ago!
好啦  我们也还在餐厅工作
Okay, we're still at the diner too.
这里  那里  到处都有我们
We're here, we're there, we're all over.
就像疱疹
Like herpes?
-接得好  -妙哉
- Nice. - Yeah.
今日是什么风把你吹来
So what brings you over here
除了摆明是来偷窥前女友之外
besides obviously stalking your ex-girlfriend?
其实我是来附近找花店的
Actually, I'm looking for a flower shop.
给你一直忘不了的女人送花吗
Oh, flowers for a girl you never got over?
不是  是给我未婚妻的
Uh, no, for my fiance.
他刚才说了碧昂丝[音似]吗
Did he just say Beyonce?
其实我要结婚了
Actually, I'm getting married.
行
Cool.
卡洛琳  抱歉
Caroline, I'm sorry.
我有想过打给你  告诉你这事
I was gonna call you and tell you,
但我又想  也许你根本懒得知道
but then I felt like maybe you wouldn't care.
毕竟我们分手也好长一段时日了
You know, I mean, it's been a long time.
希望没伤到你心
I hope you're not hurt.
伤心  我当然伤心啦
Hurt? I'm hurt.
因为你没找我跟麦克斯做婚礼蛋糕而伤心
Hurt that you didn't ask me and Max to do your wedding cake!
我去  我还是先下楼了
Oh, God. I'll be downstairs.
好吧
Well, yeah.
其实罗米跟我还没决定要哪个蛋糕
Actually, Romy and I haven't decided on a cake yet.
她满忙的  她自己经营个生意
You know, she's pretty busy. She runs her own business.
"商界新娘"呀
"The Business Bride."
这不是凯瑟琳·海格尔上一部电影的情节吗
Wasn't that Katherine Heigl's last movie?
就是把她踢回电视圈的那部烂片
The one that brought her back to TV?
麦克斯  你可以回来楼上了吗
Max, can you please come back upstairs?
我在等电梯上楼呢
I'm waiting for the elevator!
这不是糖果安迪吗
Is that Candy Andy?
哎哟哟
Well, well.
你们俩又重修旧好了吗
You two getting back together again?
-我要结婚了  -新娘不是她
- Oh, I'm getting married. - To someone else.
我去  这就是为什么我不爱出来外面
Oh, Lord, this is why I don't like to be outside.
好了  我得先滚了
Well, I gotta run.
也不是真滚  我会走掉
Not really. I'll be walking away.
如果你刚才说蛋糕的事情是认真的
But if you're serious about the cake...
超级无敌认真
So serious.
认真到爆炸
Major ser-I-osity!
其实  这就当我们送给你的新婚礼物吧
In fact, it's our wedding gift to you.
-我靠  -麦克斯  省省吧
- Oh, God. - Max, stop.
明明就没有楼下
There is no downstairs.
因为节操已经触底到下不去了
Yeah, it's not possible to get any lower than this.
好吧  那...
Okay, well...
我跟罗米谈过之后给你发消息吧
how about I text you after I talk to Romy?
很高兴再次见到你  卡洛琳
It was great seeing you, Caroline.
你也是  麦克斯
You too, Max.
我慢慢走掉时  你们会盯着我的小翘臀吧
You guys are gonna watch my butt as I walk away, right?
你的两片屁屁会为大爷拍"屁"叫好吗
You gonna make it clap for daddy?
拍屁是没办法了  但我可以让它来一下
I cannot make it clap, but I can make it go, "Whoo!"
几件事情
Um, couple things.
一  他还是很帅
One, he's still hot.
二  你是不是疯啦
And two, are you insane?
你想我们给你的前男友做婚礼蛋糕吗
You want us to do your ex-boyfriend's wedding cake?
麦克斯  是我甩了他的  还记得吗
Max, I broke up with him. Remember?
我可是个成熟世故  见过风浪
I'm a mature, evolved, sophisticated,
带有低调性感的女人
sexy but not in your face about it woman.
我能行
I can handle this.
我觉得这主意烂透了
I think it's a bad idea.
烂主意我特了解  我就是别人生的"烂主意"
And I know bad ideas. I was one.
是
I...
老娘  甩了  他
broke up... with him.
戏剧化的  说话方式
Dramatic... talking...
超  欠扁
is... annoying.
还好吗  火辣帅哥
How's it going there, hot stuff?
你的舌头好使了吗
Is your tongue working?
我得再想另一个能爆红的影片内容
I'm gonna think of another video to go viral
来让这里生意红红火火  如果还不行
to set this place on fire, and if not,
总有天我得把这店一把火烧到红红火火
I'll eventually have to set this place on fire.
无论如何  我决不放弃
Either way, I'm not giving up.
你有跟你的衣服这么说吗
You tell your clothes that?
它们感觉都放弃治疗了
'Cause they didn't get the memo.
听我说  安迪说他跟罗米
Get this. Andy says that he and Romy
很乐意跟我们见面谈婚礼蛋糕的事
would love to meet us to talk about wedding cakes
去它们曼哈顿的阁楼公寓谈
at their loft in Manhattan.
罗米皇后宣召我们两位草民
Queen Romy has summoned us
进公寓城堡谈试吃蛋糕事宜呢
to a cake tasting at their loft!
我能借用一下你的手机吗
Uh, can I borrow your phone for a sec?
好了  我删了他的短信
There. I deleted his text.
删了他的号码
I deleted his number.
还顺便把我的号码也删了
I also deleted my number.
我们不接这活儿  你没这么大度
We aren't doing this. You are not that cool.
全世界都知道
Everyone knows that.
你真不是  酷妹们才不会因为
You're not. Cool girls don't freak out
在冷冻库里被人摸奶就吓到
when you cop a feel in the freezer.
你心里会默背他的号码
You know his number by heart.
这跟我心里没有关系
This has nothing to do with my heart.
这是纯生意往来  是我甩了他
It's business. I broke up with him.
你怎么感觉好像不知道是我甩了他啊
It's like you don't know that I broke up with him.
是我甩了他  不知道你刚才有没听到
I broke up with him. Didn't know if you caught that
因为我刚才背对你
'cause my back was to you.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
好消息宣布
Good news!
我的宝宝今日送到[出生]啦
My baby was delivered today.
我的老天爷啊
Oh, my God!
我又断片九个月了吗
Did I black out for nine months again?
厄尔  这个宝宝不是从我下面出来的
The baby didn't come out of my box, Earl.
是从这盒[阴部]里出来的
It came out of this one.
这年头网上购物真是啥都能买啊
Wow, you can really get anything on Amazon.
这个叫"或许宝宝"
It's called a "Maybe Baby."
在我一边跟奥列格试图怀孩子的这会
While Oleg and I are trying to get pregnant,
我们打算用这个来为之后的孩子做练习
we're gonna use it to practice for the real thing.
所以你这是"剖盒产"吗
So you're having a key-section?
奇怪的是  这并不是我在这家餐厅
Strangely, this is not the weirdest birth
见过最怪的一次生小孩
we've seen at the diner.
你喜欢他吗
Do you like him?
你不是电影《美国狙击手》里的那个假娃娃吗
Weren't you the baby in "American Sniper"?
他里面有个小型电脑
Yeah, it's got a computer inside to keep track
给我们带孩子的技术打分
of our parenting skills.
如果我们能得到超过92分
And if we get a score of over 92,
我们去棒约翰披萨店能打8折
we get 20% at Papa John's.
任何分店呢
Any Papa John's!
你弄假婴儿的理由  全都太"正确"了
Well, you're having a fake baby for all the right reasons.
宝宝到了吗
The baby's here?
你的父亲  快接
Aww, you're a father. Think fast!
我们首次父子玩抛接
Our first father-son catch.
我们来了解一下彼此
Let's get to know each other...
"鲍伯"
"Bob"?
他们只剩下白人孩子
All they had left were the white babies.
40岁以上的单身女演员把少数种族全抢了
The single actresses over 40 snap up all the minorities.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
或许你明日愿意照看我的或许宝宝吗
Could you maybe babysit my Maybe Baby tomorrow?
因为我真的很需要一点私人的时间
You know, 'cause I-I really need some me time.
行  20块一小时
Fine. 20 bucks an hour.
如果他点播了我想看很久的成人电影
Extra in case he orders some adult movies
那我得加收一点
I've been wanting to see.
麦克斯  洗好你的上档次运动裤
Okay, Max, wash your fancy sweatpants.
我们已经确定好明日要去让
We are confirmed for Andy and Romy's
安迪与罗米试吃婚礼蛋糕了
wedding cake tasting for tomorrow.
安迪  你是说那个
Andy? You mean that cute guy
感情被你给搅黄的小帅哥吗
that you ruined your relationship with?
苏菲  那段恋情并不适合
Sophie, it wasn't the right relationship.
他不支持我的事业
He didn't support my career.
小蛋糕那玩意儿吗
The cupcake thing?
上菜
Pickup!
有其父必有其子啊
Like father like son.
你们大老远过来真是太谢谢你们了
Thank you guys so much for coming.
这些蛋糕看起来好棒
These cakes look so lovely.
的确很赞
They are.
你这屋子很不错啊
Really nice place you got here.
我注意到了你们的浴室有门
I noticed there was a door on the bathroom.
我不想炫耀  但是你去看看我们家的插座
I don't want to brag, but check out all the outlets we got.
电力十足  双头  三头
Lot of power. Two-prong, three-prong.
甚至如果你有欧洲那种奇怪的插头
You got one of those weird European plugs?
欢迎带过来用
Bring it.
他是不是很有趣
How funny is he?
对啊  他最有趣了
Oh, the funniest.
我的天啊
Oh, God.
罗米  你好像常常旅游啊
So, Romy, it looks like you travel a lot.
我很喜欢你各种...
I love all your...
小古玩[法语]
Objet d'art.
要了亲命
Oh, God.
我是个帽子设计师  我常会去马来西亚
I'm a hat designer, so I go to Malaysia
以及斯里兰卡去弄材料
and Sri Lanka a lot for materials.
我是个穷鬼  我常会去麦当劳与塔可钟
I'm poor, so I go to McDonald's and Taco Bell a lot
去吃便宜餐点
for my meals.
罗米  给她们看一顶你的帽子
Oh, show 'em one of your hats, Romes.
就是八卦杂志上那位社交名媛戴着的紫帽子
The purple one Pippa Middleton wore in "Star" Magazine.
社交名媛啊
Oh! Pippa Middleton, wow.
她本来有机会在《今日秀》得到工作呢
She was up for a job on "The Today Show,"
可惜她最后没得到
but she didn't get it.
安迪  她们才没兴趣看我设计的帽子呢
Andy, they don't want to see my hats.
安迪想我们看你的帽子
Oh, Andy wants us to see your hats.
那就看你的帽子吧
Let's see your hats.
他在没人愿意相信我的时候支持我
Oh, this guy was there when no one believed in me,
各方面都为我撑腰
and he supported me in every way,
现在我的作品在全球上百家百货都有
and now I'm in over a hundred department stores worldwide.
全球吗
Worldwide?
真是太全了
That is wide.
你知道今天是他们试吃吧
You know the tasting is for them, right?
来嘛  让她们看看
Come on, let 'em see what you do.
抱歉  我很为我未婚妻感到自豪
Sorry, I'm a proud fiance.
虽然有点娘  但我就是这样
It's a little unmanly, but it's m'thing.
我去取黑色大丽花那顶
Ooh, I'll go get Black Dahlia.
麦克斯会喜欢那顶
Max will like that one.
你还好吧
You okay?
当然啦
Absolutely.
我们感情没成  你找到了别的很棒的人
We didn't work out, you found someone great,
支持她的事业  现在还要结婚了
supported her business, and now you're getting married.
我蛮确定他是问"你没噎着吧"
Pretty sure he meant, "Are you choking?"
是的  我的确是在问这个
Yup, that's where I was headed.
卡洛琳  是你跟我分手的
Caroline, you broke up with me.
她跟你提分手的吗
She broke up with you?
我没听过这事呢
I hadn't heard that.
看  太有事  没事了
See? All bitter... better.
麦克斯  你想戴戴看吗
Max, do you want to try it on?
她不需要帽子啦
Ahem, she doesn't need a hat.
罗米说我可以戴美帽
Romes said I could have the sweet hat!
你戴真是太好看了  这顶送你吧
Oh, it looks adorable on her. You should have it.
这是啥  试吃帽子吗
What is this, a hat tasting now?
反正不是试吃小蛋糕
Well, it's not a cupcake tasting anymore
因为全被你吃完了
'cause you ate them all.
你们俩真是太有意思了  我不需要试吃啦
You guys are hilarious. I don't need to taste those.
你跟麦克斯都是安迪过去的一部分
You and Max are a part of Andy's past,
能请你们为我们做蛋糕
and I would honored if you'd do our cake
并且出席我们婚礼将会是我的荣幸
and come to the wedding as our guests.
这主意很棒  到时会有很多
Oh, that is a great idea. Hey, there will be a lot
自毁前程又长不大的男人在场
of self-destructive man-children there.
麦克斯  感觉派对上都会是你的菜
Max, feels like your kind of party.
而且是在一艘很棒的游艇上举办
And it's on this awesome yacht.
其实不是什么船都能称为游艇
You know, technically it's not a yacht
除非它超过12米以上
unless it's over 40 feet.
超过了吗  好吧
Is it? Okay.
来嘛  会很好玩的
Come on. It'll be fun.
我不知道
Gah! I don't know.
我这人不太爱玩
And I'm not really into fun.
我已经玩过太多  也没那么好玩啦
You know, I've had fun and it's not that fun.
懂了  我想什么呢
Got it. What was I thinking?
对你来说会很怪吧  卡洛琳
Be weird for you, Caroline, right?
怪什么
Weird?
我们不来才怪呢
Weird if we didn't come!
我了个老天爷啊
Oh, God.
麦克斯  你看
Look at this, Max.
小蛋糕与糖果
Cupcakes and candy.
这本来可以是我与安迪的婚礼蛋糕呢
This could have been me and Andy's cake.
我们完美婚礼的完美婚礼蛋糕
Our perfect cake for our perfect marriage.
天下无完美的婚姻  除了那对模特与饶舌歌手
No marriage is perfect... except Ice-T and Coco.
他才不完美呢
Now, he's not perfect.
你会跟他分手是有原因的
You broke up with him for a reason.
安迪现在就在隔壁  你过来
Andy's out there now. Come here.
婚礼放音乐  太有"创意"了
Music at a wedding? How original.
他就在那里
Oh, there he is.
他穿燕尾服的样子真的好帅
He looks so handsome in a tuxedo.
冷静点好吗  简·林奇穿也帅啊
Calm down. So does Jane Lynch.
他才不完美呢  你看他
He's not perfect. Look, there.
他准备要挖鼻孔了
He's going in for a nose pick.
没有  只是抓个痒
No, just a scratch.
他的手也好好看  好大的一双手
He has such nice hands. Big hands.
可是手上马上要被套上结婚戒指了
And there's gonna be a ring on it soon.
他看过来了
He's looking over here! Oh, oh!
-不能让他看到我哭  -来
- He can't see me cry! - Okay, come on.
想想他的缺点
Think of something bad about him.
快想快想快想
Think, think, think, think, think.
做爱的时候  他总是要太久才完事
Uh... he always took too long to finish during sex!
等等  这是个优点啊
Oh, wait. That's a good thing.
是咩  好吧  来
It is? All right, come on.
你们感情中肯定是有哪里
There had to be something terribly wrong
大错特错
with that relationship.
有的  就是我结束了这段感情
There was. That I ended it.
我把完美的那人从我生命中踢走
I kicked the perfect guy for me out of my life.
我的眼泪要下来了
Yup, here come the tears.
安迪也要过来了
And here comes Andy!
这里有厕所吗
Uh, do you have a bathroom? Oh!
我就觉得好像看到了你们俩在这边偷看
Hey! Thought I saw you guys peeking out of here.
所以你们俩是到哪都怪里怪气的吗
So you guys act weird everywhere?
没错  这是我们的招牌
Yup, that's our signature.
害我们去主题公园时被赶出来
Got us bounced out of Six Flags.
卡洛琳呢
Where's Caroline?
上美女厕了
The pretty ladies' room.
看来你要结婚了啊
So it looks like you're getting married
跟"非卡洛琳"
to Not Caroline.
她还好吗
How's she doing?
我感觉她来婚礼好像挺难受
I'm getting the feeling this has been hard for her.
测测温度
Temperature check.
我不太懂你什么意思
Okay, I don't understand.
是要我撅起屁股量肛温吗
Are you asking me to bend over?
要是卡洛琳觉得自己犯了错误
What if Caroline thought she might have made a mistake
不该跟你分手  你会愿意考虑
by breaking up with you? Would you consider being
当逃跑新郎  再给你们俩感情一次机会吗
a runaway groom and giving it another shot with her?
只是个想法而已
Just a thought.
我得告诉你  一切为时已晚
Well, I guess I'd have to say it's too late.
我要跟罗米结婚了  我爱她
I'm getting married to Romy. I love her.
所以是确定不可能啦
So that's a firm no?
麦克斯
Uh, Max.
您请便
All yours now.
我们就假装没听到刚才的话
How about we pretend like none of this happened
你们俩等会出来看我成婚  好吗
and you guys come watch me get married, okay?
安迪  等等
Andy, wait.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我真心为你感到开心
I really am happy for you.
去过你的人生  我愿你一生幸福
Go live your life. I wish you well.
谢谢  你这话对我意义非凡
Thank you. That means a lot to me.
我曾经真的爱过你
I really did love you.
我知道
I know.
尽管最后你与我分了手
Even though you broke up with me.
是啊  尽管最后我与你分了手
Yeah, even though I broke up with you.
我做到了  我没哭
I did it. I didn't cry.
麦克斯  怎么了
Max, what's wrong?
你本来可以拥有一切美好
You could have had it all!
麦克斯  我从来没见你哭过
Max, I've never seen you cry.